Sit down.
So, tell me what's going on.
What do you want to talk about? Whatever you want to talk about.
Ask me a question.
Am I still sexy?
I don't want to answer that question.
Yes.
Thank you.
Um...
One thing we should go over. Teach people how to use this.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
So when I gave this to you for my first time, what do you think?
I was, like...
Inside, I was, like, a little kid jumping up and down, like, I
just won the biggest raffle in the world.
Because... I
had previously just told our therapist, Lady Rebecca, that I just need, like, leadership, and I need things in writing, and I need to see, I need, like, tactile
stuff to, like, organize our family.
And then
you come up, and you're like, and I told her I wanted to get better at, like, budgeting my
expenses, and you, like, covered all of it.
It's like.
What is it? Okay, it's the Sunday board meeting.
It's a weekly check in for couples who lead together.
There's a section on here where we need to talk about money.
Like, what are some upcoming expenses?
What are some financial decisions we have to make this week?
Um, household operations, like, just touching base on, like, what are the meals gonna
be, what groceries do we need?
Any home projects going on this week?
The kids' needs, family needs.
And then, I'm going in a backwards order.
It starts with connection and check in, which I think is good.
So, the husband's checking in, and, like, how are we doing?
On a scale of one to 10?
Emotional connection, physical intimacy, communication.
One thing I can do this week to support you better.
So, it's just a lot of, like, jumping off points of
all the things that are usually on people's minds, both partners' minds.
Almost daily or throughout the week that
you just don't have time to sit down and talk about, you know, on these busy days.
So this kind of just, like, gets your week started off right.
And then there's a schedule.
So you talk about, like, what's happening every day, and you can write it down, because we
all know. We've said, hey, honey,
we've got dinner with Grandma Gigi on Tuesday.
Don't forget. Grandma Gigi.
Yeah. That's her name. I need you to meet us at her house at 5:30.
Well, it's not gonna be remembered.
Anyway, no, happens to both of us.
But, yeah, it's all written down, so that's good.
She likes it.
Yeah. Oh, and then there's us time, planning a date night, and then a family adventure,
like one a week, which is amazing.
That's what our weekends should be made up of, right?
Family adventures.